<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<items>
<item><Ime>Mirco GT 3D seat</Ime><Kratki opis>The new, improved version ensures perfect grip. Shell is made from light, high quality fiberglass.  </Kratki opis><SKU> CRO113GELGR </SKU><Cena>271,94 €</Cena><Opis>We offer you one of the most popular racing FIA Approved seat in Europe.The new, improved version ensures perfect grip. Shell is made from light, high quality fiberglass. The GT 3D offers amazing sport-like looks with its red and black colour scheme, along with high quality red stitching, and is sure to make the driver feel more eager to win. The 3D material helps with ventilation during hot conditions, where the driver is prone to sweat. Thanks to the deep sitting position of the GT 3D, the driver can feel safe and comfortable in their seat and don't have to worry about moving around much. Monolithic construction seat: - made of high durability glass fiber reinforced plastic shell mould- 5 harness slot, can be used with 4, 5 or 6 point race harnesses- maximum recommended driver dimensions: ~ 85 kg / 185 cm Mirco GT seat has the latest FIA homologation that allows you to take part in all FIA events across the World!!





</Opis><Slike><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-gt-3d_66.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-gt-3d_67.jpg</value></Slike><Features>Fixing: Side Weight: 8,2 kg Approval: FIA 8855-1999 Cover: 3D</Features></item>
<item><Ime>Mirco GT Olive seat</Ime><Kratki opis>The new, improved version ensures perfect grip. Shell is made from light, high quality fiberglass.  </Kratki opis><SKU> CRO113SKVE </SKU><Cena>271,94 €</Cena><Opis>We offer you one of the most popular racing FIA Approved seat in Europe.The new, improved version ensures perfect grip. Shell is made from light, high quality fiberglass. The Mirco GT Olive FIA-approved seat offers great sleek looks while not compromising on safety or comfort. Its green colour is perfect for darker interiors as well as lighter ones. Thanks to its cover made of artificial leather and velour, the GT Olive offers amazing comfort, durability, safety, and is very easy to maintain thanks to the design. Thanks to the deep sitting position of the GT Olive, the driver can feel safe and comfortable in their seat and don't have to worry about moving around much. Monolithic construction seat: - made of high durability glass fiber reinforced plastic shell mould- 5 harness slot, can be used with 4, 5 or 6 point race harnesses- maximum recommended driver dimensions: ~ 85 kg / 185 cm Mirco GT seat has the latest FIA homologation that allows you to take part in all FIA events across the World!!





</Opis><Slike><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-gt-olive_56.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-gt-olive_57.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-gt-olive_58.jpg</value></Slike><Features>Fixing: Side Weight: 8,2 kg Approval: FIA 8855-1999 Cover: Artificial leather + velours</Features></item>
<item><Ime>Mirco RS1 Vinyl seat</Ime><Kratki opis>Ideal offer for those who seeks comfortable, modern design racing seat.</Kratki opis><SKU> CRO111VINYL </SKU><Cena>360,39 €</Cena><Opis>We offer you one of the most popular racing FIA Approved seat in Europe. Ideal offer for those who seeks comfortable, modern design racing seat. Mirco seats are made of reinforced polyester - glass, characterized by high strength, ensuring the safety and comfort of use. The new, improved version ensures perfect grip. Shell is made from light, high quality fiberglass. The Mirco RS1 Vinyl is a slim seat built with safety in mind thanks to its ears that help to protect the driver's head in case of a side collision. Due to its slim design, the RS1 is a better fit for people with a smaller physique, however for a wider similar FIA-approved seat you can try out the RS2. Thanks to the all-artificial-leather design of the cover, the RS1 Vinyl is very easy to maintain and will withstand a lot of stress over a long period of time. Also, thanks to the orange stitching, the colour contrast of the RS1 Vinyl is very sports-like. Monolithic construction seat: - Upholstered In velvet material- Made of high durability glass fiber reinforced plastic shell mould- 5 harness slot, can be used with 4, 5 or 6 point race harnesses- Maximum recommended driver dimensions: 85 kg / 185 cm tall  Mirco RTS seat has the latest FIA homologation that allows you to take part in all FIA events across the World!!!










</Opis><Slike><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs1-vinyl_301.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs1-vinyl_303.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs1-vinyl_304.jpg</value></Slike><Features>Fixing: Side Weight: 8,6 kg Approval: FIA 8855-1999 Cover: Artificial leather</Features></item>
<item><Ime>Mirco GT Grid seat</Ime><Kratki opis>The new, improved version ensures perfect grip. Shell is made from light, high quality fiberglass.  </Kratki opis><SKU> CRO113SKNRPER </SKU><Cena>271,94 €</Cena><Opis>We offer you one of the most popular racing FIA Approved seat in Europe.The new, improved version ensures perfect grip. Shell is made from light, high quality fiberglass. With its grid design, the Mirco GT Grid is perfect for drivers that would like a seat without comprimising the factory look of the car. The seat cover is made from artificial leather for easy maintenance as well as velour for great looks and comfort. Thanks to the deep sitting position of the GT Grid, the driver can feel safe and comfortable in their seat and don't have to worry about moving around much. Monolithic construction seat: - made of high durability glass fiber reinforced plastic shell mould- 5 harness slot, can be used with 4, 5 or 6 point race harnesses- maximum recommended driver dimensions: ~ 85 kg / 185 cm Mirco GT seat has the latest FIA homologation that allows you to take part in all FIA events across the World!!





</Opis><Slike><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-gt-grid_59.jpg</value></Slike><Features>Fixing: Side Weight: 8,2 kg Approval: FIA 8855-1999 Cover: Artificial leather + velours</Features></item>
<item><Ime>Mirco GT Gel Gray seat</Ime><Kratki opis>The new, improved version ensures perfect grip. Shell is made from light, high quality fiberglass.  </Kratki opis><SKU> CRO113GELGR </SKU><Cena>282,05 €</Cena><Opis>We offer you one of the most popular racing FIA Approved seat in Europe.The new, improved version ensures perfect grip. Shell is made from light, high quality fiberglass. With its sleek and unibody design, the Mirco GT Gel Gray is the perfect FIA approved seat for both dark and light car interiors. It is covered in an all-grey velour with grey stitching with black cut-outs for a great design. Thanks to the deep sitting position of the GT Gel Gray, the driver can feel safe and comfortable in their seat and don't have to worry about moving around much. Monolithic construction seat: - made of high durability glass fiber reinforced plastic shell mould- 5 harness slot, can be used with 4, 5 or 6 point race harnesses- maximum recommended driver dimensions: ~ 85 kg / 185 cm Mirco GT seat has the latest FIA homologation that allows you to take part in all FIA events across the World!!




</Opis><Slike><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-gt-gel-gray_63.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-gt-gel-gray_64.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-gt-gel-gray_65.jpg</value></Slike><Features>Fixing: Side Weight: 8,2 kg Approval: FIA 8855-1999 Cover: Velour</Features></item>
<item><Ime>Mirco GT Classic seat</Ime><Kratki opis>None</Kratki opis><SKU> CRO113SKMA </SKU><Cena>271,94 €</Cena><Opis>We offer you one of the most popular racing FIA Approved seat in Europe.The new, improved version ensures perfect grip. Shell is made from light, high quality fiberglass. The GT Classic is covered in a classic-style velour, offering great comfort and old-school racing looks. With its FIA homologation and great side support, the driver is sure to feel safe in this seat. The seat is coverer with artificial leather for easy maintenance as well as velour for great looks and comfort. Thanks to the deep sitting position of the GT Classic, the driver can feel safe and comfortable in their seat and don't have to worry about moving around much.
 Monolithic construction seat: - made of high durability glass fiber reinforced plastic shell mould- 5 harness slot, can be used with 4, 5 or 6 point race harnesses- maximum recommended driver dimensions: ~ 85 kg / 185 cm Mirco GT seat has the latest FIA homologation that allows you to take part in all FIA events across the World!!





</Opis><Slike><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-gt-classic_52.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-gt-classic_53.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-gt-classic_54.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-gt-classic_55.jpg</value></Slike><Features>Fixing: Side Weight: 8,2 kg Approval: FIA 8855-1999 Cover: Artificial leather + velours</Features></item>
<item><Ime>Mirco RS1 3D seat</Ime><Kratki opis>Ideal offer for those who seeks comfortable, modern design racing seat.</Kratki opis><SKU> CRO111NR3D </SKU><Cena>348,66 €</Cena><Opis>We offer you one of the most popular racing FIA Approved seat in Europe. Ideal offer for those who seeks comfortable, modern design racing seat. Mirco seats are made of reinforced polyester - glass, characterized by high strength, ensuring the safety and comfort of use. The new, improved version ensures perfect grip. Shell is made from light, high quality fiberglass. The Mirco RS1 3D is a slim seat built with safety in mind thanks to its ears that help to protect the driver's head in case of a side collision. Due to its slim design, the RS1 is a better fit for people with a smaller physique, however for a wider similar FIA-approved seat you can try out the RS2. The dark colour scheme and stitching differentiates this seat from others by giving it an agressive look and would look good in any vehicle interior. Monolithic construction seat: - Upholstered In velvet material- Made of high durability glass fiber reinforced plastic shell mould- 5 harness slot, can be used with 4, 5 or 6 point race harnesses- Maximum recommended driver dimensions: 85 kg / 185 cm tall  Mirco RTS seat has the latest FIA homologation that allows you to take part in all FIA events across the World!!!










</Opis><Slike><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs1-3d-seat_387.jpg</value></Slike><Features>Fixing: Side Weight: 8,6 kg Approval: FIA 8855-1999 Cover: 3D</Features></item>
<item><Ime>Mirco GT Race Gel seat</Ime><Kratki opis>The new, improved version ensures perfect grip. Shell is made from light, high quality fiberglass.   </Kratki opis><SKU> CRO113GEL </SKU><Cena>296,18 €</Cena><Opis>We offer you one of the most popular racing FIA Approved seat in Europe.The new, improved version ensures perfect grip. Shell is made from light, high quality fiberglass. The Mirco GT Race Gel seat offers amazing sport-like looks with its dark colour scheme, along with high quality red stitching, and is sure to make the driver feel more eager to win. Thanks to the velour cover, the seat is comfortable to sit in and replace in case there is a need to. Thanks to the deep sitting position of the GT Race Gel, the driver can feel safe and comfortable in their seat and don't have to worry about moving around much. Monolithic construction seat: - made of high durability glass fiber reinforced plastic shell mould- 5 harness slot, can be used with 4, 5 or 6 point race harnesses- maximum recommended driver dimensions: ~ 85 kg / 185 cm Mirco GT seat has the latest FIA homologation that allows you to take part in all FIA events across the World!!





</Opis><Slike><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-gt-race-gel_60.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-gt-race-gel_61.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-gt-race-gel_62.jpg</value></Slike><Features>Fixing: Side Colour: Black Weight: 8,2 kg Approval: FIA 8855-1999 Cover: Velour</Features></item>
<item><Ime>Mirco RS1 Colore seat</Ime><Kratki opis>Ideal offer for those who seeks comfortable, modern design racing seat.</Kratki opis><SKU> CRO111... </SKU><Cena>325,47 €</Cena><Opis>We offer you one of the most popular racing FIA Approved seat in Europe. Ideal offer for those who seeks comfortable, modern design racing seat. Mirco seats are made of reinforced polyester - glass, characterized by high strength, ensuring the safety and comfort of use. The new, improved version ensures perfect grip. Shell is made from light, high quality fiberglass. The Mirco RS1 Colore is a slim seat built with safety in mind thanks to its ears that help to protect the driver's head in case of a side collision. Due to its slim design, the RS1 is a better fit for people with a smaller physique, however for a wider similar FIA-approved seat you can try out the RS2. The RS1 Colore is available in many different colours, therefore being perfect for cars with colourful interiors or even exteriors. Thanks to the velour finish of the seat cover, the seat has a premium quality and a great feel for the driver. Monolithic construction seat: - Upholstered In velvet material- Made of high durability glass fiber reinforced plastic shell mould- 5 harness slot, can be used with 4, 5 or 6 point race harnesses- Maximum recommended driver dimensions: 85 kg / 185 cm tall  Mirco RTS seat has the latest FIA homologation that allows you to take part in all FIA events across the World!!!










</Opis><Slike><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs1-colour_305.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs1-colour_306.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs1-colour_307.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs1-colour_308.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs1-colour_309.jpg</value></Slike><Features>Fixing: Side Weight: 8,6 kg Approval: FIA 8855-1999 Cover: Velour</Features></item>
<item><Ime>Mirco RS1 seat</Ime><Kratki opis>Ideal offer for those who seeks comfortable, modern design racing seat.</Kratki opis><SKU> CRO111 </SKU><Cena>325,47 €</Cena><Opis>We offer you one of the most popular racing FIA Approved seat in Europe. Ideal offer for those who seeks comfortable, modern design racing seat. Mirco seats are made of reinforced polyester - glass, characterized by high strength, ensuring the safety and comfort of use. The new, improved version ensures perfect grip. Shell is made from light, high quality fiberglass. The Mirco RS1 is a slim seat built with safety in mind thanks to its ears that help to protect the driver's head in case of a side collision. Due to its slim design, the RS1 is a better fit for people with a smaller physique, however for a wider similar FIA-approved seat you can try out the RS2. This seat is perfect for darker interiors due to its dark colour scheme, although it would also look great in a lighter interior. Monolithic construction seat: - Upholstered In velvet material- Made of high durability glass fiber reinforced plastic shell mould- 5 harness slot, can be used with 4, 5 or 6 point race harnesses- Maximum recommended driver dimensions: 85 kg / 185 cm tall  Mirco RTS seat has the latest FIA homologation that allows you to take part in all FIA events across the World!!!










</Opis><Slike><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs1_24.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs1_25.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs1_26.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs1_27.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs1_28.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs1_29.jpg</value></Slike><Features>Fixing: Side Weight: 8,6 kg Approval: FIA 8855-1999 Cover: Velour</Features></item>
<item><Ime>Mirco GT seat</Ime><Kratki opis>We offer you one of the most popular racing FIA Approved seat in Europe.  </Kratki opis><SKU> CRO113... </SKU><Cena>243,88 €</Cena><Opis>We offer you one of the most popular racing FIA Approved seat in Europe.The new, improved version ensures perfect grip. Shell is made from light, high quality fiberglass. The original GT sports an all-black velour design with black stitching all across. Perfect for darker interiors. Thanks to the deep sitting position of the GT, the driver can feel safe and comfortable in their seat and don't have to worry about moving around much.
 Monolithic construction seat: - made of high durability glass fiber reinforced plastic shell mould- 5 harness slot, can be used with 4, 5 or 6 point race harnesses- maximum recommended driver dimensions: ~ 85 kg / 185 cm Mirco GT seat has the latest FIA homologation that allows you to take part in all FIA events across the World!!





</Opis><Slike><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/p/produkt-testowy_8.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-gt_12.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-gt_13.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-gt_14.jpg</value></Slike><Features>Fixing: Side Weight: 8,2 kg Approval: FIA 8855-1999 Cover: Velour</Features></item>
<item><Ime>Mirco GT Khaki seat</Ime><Kratki opis>We offer you one of the most popular racing FIA Approved seat in Europe.</Kratki opis><SKU> CRO113CA </SKU><Cena>271,94 €</Cena><Opis>We offer you one of the most popular racing FIA Approved seat in Europe.The new, improved version ensures perfect grip. Shell is made from light, high quality fiberglass. The Mirco GT Khaki is the perfect seat for drivers that like to show off their car with its great looks. Its camo-like looks is sure to impress everyone and the fiberglass construction along with velour covering ensures maximum comfort as well as safety in case of a collision. Thanks to the deep sitting position of the GT Khaki, the driver can feel safe and comfortable in their seat and don't have to worry about moving around much. Monolithic construction seat: - made of high durability glass fiber reinforced plastic shell mould- 5 harness slot, can be used with 4, 5 or 6 point race harnesses- maximum recommended driver dimensions: ~ 85 kg / 185 cm Mirco GT seat has the latest FIA homologation that allows you to take part in all FIA events across the World!!




</Opis><Slike><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-gt-khaki_19.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-gt-khaki_20.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-gt-khaki_21.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-gt-khaki_22.jpg</value></Slike><Features>Fixing: Side Weight: 8,2 kg Approval: FIA 8855-1999 Cover: Velour</Features></item>
<item><Ime>Mirco RS2 3D Limited Edition seat</Ime><Kratki opis>Mirco seats are made of reinforced polyester - glass, characterized by high strength, ensuring the safety and comfort of use.  </Kratki opis><SKU> CRO110... </SKU><Cena>358,10 €</Cena><Opis>















</Opis><Slike><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs2-3d-limited-edition_310.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs2-3d-limited-edition_311.jpg</value></Slike><Features>Fixing: Side Weight: 9,3 kg Approval: FIA 8855-1999 Cover: 3D</Features></item>
<item><Ime>Mirco RS2 3D Racing seat</Ime><Kratki opis>Mirco seats are made of reinforced polyester - glass, characterized by high strength, ensuring the safety and comfort of use.  </Kratki opis><SKU> CRO110... </SKU><Cena>358,10 €</Cena><Opis>We offer you one of the most popular racing FIA Approved seat in Europe. Ideal offer for those who seeks comfortable, modern design racing seat. Mirco seats are made of reinforced polyester - glass, characterized by high strength, ensuring the safety and comfort of use. The new, improved version ensures perfect grip. Shell is made from light, high quality fiberglass. The Mirco RS2 is a wider version of the RS1, manufacturered by Mirco for users of a larger physique. Similar to RS1 seats, the RS2 consists of ears that protect the driver's head in the event of a side collision. The RS2 also has removable lumbar and leg supports to allow the driver to position the seat to their most comfortable position. The deep seating position also aids with comfort during races and regular driving. Thanks to the 3D material of the seat cover, the driver doesn't have to worry about overheating in warmer climates as the seat helps with ventilation. The 3D material is of very high quality and is guaranteed to last a very long time.  Monolithic construction seat: - Upholstered In velvet material- Made of high durability glass fiber reinforced plastic shell mould- 5 harness slot, can be used with 4, 5 or 6 point race harnesses- Maximum recommended driver dimensions: 95 kg / 190 cm tall  Mirco RTS seat has the latest FIA homologation that allows you to take part in all FIA events across the World!!!










</Opis><Slike><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs2-3d-racing_318.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs2-3d-racing_319.jpg</value></Slike><Features>Fixing: Side Weight: 9,3 kg Approval: FIA 8855-1999 Cover: 3D</Features></item>
<item><Ime>Mirco RS2 3D Tuning seat</Ime><Kratki opis>Mirco seats are made of reinforced polyester - glass, characterized by high strength, ensuring the safety and comfort of use.  </Kratki opis><SKU> CRO110... </SKU><Cena>358,10 €</Cena><Opis>We offer you one of the most popular racing FIA Approved seat in Europe. Ideal offer for those who seeks comfortable, modern design racing seat. Mirco seats are made of reinforced polyester - glass, characterized by high strength, ensuring the safety and comfort of use. The new, improved version ensures perfect grip. Shell is made from light, high quality fiberglass. The Mirco RS2 is a wider version of the RS1, manufacturered by Mirco for users of a larger physique. Similar to RS1 seats, the RS2 consists of ears that protect the driver's head in the event of a side collision. The RS2 also has removable lumbar and leg supports to allow the driver to position the seat to their most comfortable position. The deep seating position also aids with comfort during races and regular driving. Monolithic construction seat: - Upholstered In velvet material- Made of high durability glass fiber reinforced plastic shell mould- 5 harness slot, can be used with 4, 5 or 6 point race harnesses- Maximum recommended driver dimensions: 95 kg / 190 cm tall  Mirco RTS seat has the latest FIA homologation that allows you to take part in all FIA events across the World!!!










</Opis><Slike><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs2-3d-tuning_323.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs2-3d-tuning_324.jpg</value></Slike><Features>Fixing: Side Weight: 9,3 kg Approval: FIA 8855-1999 Cover: 3D</Features></item>
<item><Ime>Mirco RS2 Blue seat</Ime><Kratki opis>Mirco seats are made of reinforced polyester - glass, characterized by high strength, ensuring the safety and comfort of use.  </Kratki opis><SKU> CRO110AZ3D </SKU><Cena>334,63 €</Cena><Opis>We offer you one of the most popular racing FIA Approved seat in Europe. Ideal offer for those who seeks comfortable, modern design racing seat. Mirco seats are made of reinforced polyester - glass, characterized by high strength, ensuring the safety and comfort of use. The new, improved version ensures perfect grip. Shell is made from light, high quality fiberglass. The Mirco RS2 Blue seat is a wider version of the RS1, manufacturered by Mirco for users of a larger physique. Similar to RS1 seats, the RS2 consists of ears that protect the driver's head in the event of a side collision. The RS2 Blue also has removable lumbar and leg supports to allow the driver to position the seat to their most comfortable position. The deep seating position also aids with comfort during races and regular driving. The traditional blue colour of the Mirco RS2 is recogniseable all over the world, and is the perfect seat for cars with darker as well as light interiors.Monolithic construction seat: - Upholstered In velvet material- Made of high durability glass fiber reinforced plastic shell mould- 5 harness slot, can be used with 4, 5 or 6 point race harnesses- Maximum recommended driver dimensions: 95 kg / 190 cm tall  Mirco RTS seat has the latest FIA homologation that allows you to take part in all FIA events across the World!!!










</Opis><Slike><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs2-blue_317.jpg</value></Slike><Features>Fixing: Side Weight: 9,3 kg Approval: FIA 8855-1999 Cover: 3D</Features></item>
<item><Ime>Mirco RTS 3D seat</Ime><Kratki opis> Mirco seats are made of reinforced polyester - glass, characterized by high strength, ensuring the safety and comfort of use. </Kratki opis><SKU> CRO112NR3D </SKU><Cena>283,67 €</Cena><Opis>Monolithic construction seat: - Upholstered In velvet material- Made of high durability glass fiber reinforced plastic shell mould- 5 harness slots, can be used with 4, 5 or 6 point race harnesses- maximum recommended driver dimensions: ~ 100 kg / 190 cm 










</Opis><Slike><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rts-3d_386.jpg</value></Slike><Features>Fixing: Side Weight: 8,8 kg Approval: FIA 8855-1999 Cover: 3D</Features></item>
<item><Ime>Mirco RS2 Vinyl seat</Ime><Kratki opis>Mirco seats are made of reinforced polyester - glass, characterized by high strength, ensuring the safety and comfort of use.  </Kratki opis><SKU> CRO110... </SKU><Cena>367,27 €</Cena><Opis>We offer you one of the most popular racing FIA Approved seat in Europe. Ideal offer for those who seeks comfortable, modern design racing seat. Mirco seats are made of reinforced polyester - glass, characterized by high strength, ensuring the safety and comfort of use. The new, improved version ensures perfect grip. Shell is made from light, high quality fiberglass. The Mirco RS2 is a wider version of the RS1, manufacturered by Mirco for users of a larger physique. Similar to RS1 seats, the RS2 consists of ears that protect the driver's head in the event of a side collision. The RS2 also has removable lumbar and leg supports to allow the driver to position the seat to their most comfortable position. The deep seating position also aids with comfort during races and regular driving. RS2 Vinyl seats are trimmed in vinyl, making them perfect for off-road events due to the simple cleaning process. The 3D material is of very high quality and is guaranteed to last a long time. Monolithic construction seat: - Upholstered In velvet material- Made of high durability glass fiber reinforced plastic shell mould- 5 harness slot, can be used with 4, 5 or 6 point race harnesses- Maximum recommended driver dimensions: 95 kg / 190 cm tall  Mirco RTS seat has the latest FIA homologation that allows you to take part in all FIA events across the World!!!










</Opis><Slike><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs2-vinyl_320.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs2-vinyl_321.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs2-vinyl_322.jpg</value></Slike><Features>Fixing: Side Weight: 9,3 kg Approval: FIA 8855-1999 Cover: 3D</Features></item>
<item><Ime>Mirco RS2 seat</Ime><Kratki opis>Mirco seats are made of reinforced polyester - glass, characterized by high strength, ensuring the safety and comfort of use.  </Kratki opis><SKU> CRO110... </SKU><Cena>334,63 €</Cena><Opis>We offer you one of the most popular racing FIA Approved seat in Europe. Ideal offer for those who seeks comfortable, modern design racing seat. Mirco seats are made of reinforced polyester - glass, characterized by high strength, ensuring the safety and comfort of use. The new, improved version ensures perfect grip. Shell is made from light, high quality fiberglass. The Mirco RS2 is a wider version of the RS1, manufacturered by Mirco for users of a larger physique. Similar to RS1 seats, the RS2 consists of ears that protect the driver's head in the event of a side collision. The RS2 also has removable lumbar and leg supports to allow the driver to position the seat to their most comfortable position. The deep seating position also aids with comfort during races and regular driving. Monolithic construction seat: - Upholstered In velvet material- Made of high durability glass fiber reinforced plastic shell mould- 5 harness slot, can be used with 4, 5 or 6 point race harnesses- Maximum recommended driver dimensions: 95 kg / 190 cm tall  Mirco RTS seat has the latest FIA homologation that allows you to take part in all FIA events across the World!!!










</Opis><Slike><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs2_312.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs2_313.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs2_314.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs2_315.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs2_316.jpg</value></Slike><Features>Fixing: Side Weight: 9,3 kg Approval: FIA 8855-1999 Cover: Velour</Features></item>
<item><Ime>Mirco RTS seat</Ime><Kratki opis> Mirco seats are made of reinforced polyester - glass, characterized by high strength, ensuring the safety and comfort of use. </Kratki opis><SKU> CRO112... </SKU><Cena>255,62 €</Cena><Opis>We offer you one of the most popular racing FIA Approved seat in Europe. Ideal offer for those who seeks comfortable, modern design racing seat. Mirco seats are made of reinforced polyester - glass, characterized by high strength, ensuring the safety and comfort of use. The new, improved version ensures perfect grip. Shell is made from light, high quality fiberglass. The Mirco RTS offers a great sleek design that is sure to impress anyone. Thanks to its removable lumbar and leg supports, the driver can tailor the seat to their configuration and what suits their  driving style. The RTS is a wider version of the Mirco GT seat, and therefore more suitable for people of a larger physique. Thanks to the deep sitting position of the RTS, the driver can feel safe and comfortable in their seat and don't have to worry about moving around much. Monolithic construction seat: - Upholstered In velvet material- Made of high durability glass fiber reinforced plastic shell mould- 5 harness slots, can be used with 4, 5 or 6 point race harnesses- maximum recommended driver dimensions: ~ 100 kg / 190 cm Mirco RTS seat has the latest FIA homologation that allows you to take part in all FIA events across the World!!!





</Opis><Slike><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rts_69.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rts_77.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rts_300.jpg</value></Slike><Features>Fixing: Side Weight: 8,8 kg Approval: FIA 8855-1999 Cover: Velour</Features></item>
<item><Ime>Mirco RS7 seat</Ime><Kratki opis>Mirco seats are made of reinforced polyester - glass, characterized by high strength, ensuring the safety and comfort of use.  </Kratki opis><SKU> CRO123... </SKU><Cena>372,12 €</Cena><Opis>
 Cover Material: choose between velour, 3D, jacquard, artifical leather or natural leatherShell Material: made of high durability glass fiber reinforced plastic shell mouldHarness Slots: 5 harness slot, can be used with 4, 5 or 6 point race harnessesSize Guide: maximum recommended driver dimensions: 95 kg / 190 cm tall  Mirco RS7 seat is FIA homologated, meaning that you can take part in all FIA events across the World!










</Opis><Slike><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs7-seat_455.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs7-seat_456.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs7-seat_457.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs7-seat_458.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs7-seat_459.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rs7-seat_460.jpg</value></Slike><Features>Fixing: Side Weight: 9,3 kg Approval: FIA 8855-1999</Features></item>
</items>