<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<items>
<item><Ime>Mirco RTS 3D seat</Ime><Kratki opis> Mirco seats are made of reinforced polyester - glass, characterized by high strength, ensuring the safety and comfort of use. </Kratki opis><SKU> CRO112NR3D </SKU><Cena>283,67 €</Cena><Opis>Monolithic construction seat: - Upholstered In velvet material- Made of high durability glass fiber reinforced plastic shell mould- 5 harness slots, can be used with 4, 5 or 6 point race harnesses- maximum recommended driver dimensions: ~ 100 kg / 190 cm 










</Opis><Slike><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rts-3d_386.jpg</value></Slike><Features>Fixing: Side Weight: 8,8 kg Approval: FIA 8855-1999 Cover: 3D</Features></item>
<item><Ime>Mirco RTS seat</Ime><Kratki opis> Mirco seats are made of reinforced polyester - glass, characterized by high strength, ensuring the safety and comfort of use. </Kratki opis><SKU> CRO112... </SKU><Cena>255,62 €</Cena><Opis>We offer you one of the most popular racing FIA Approved seat in Europe. Ideal offer for those who seeks comfortable, modern design racing seat. Mirco seats are made of reinforced polyester - glass, characterized by high strength, ensuring the safety and comfort of use. The new, improved version ensures perfect grip. Shell is made from light, high quality fiberglass. The Mirco RTS offers a great sleek design that is sure to impress anyone. Thanks to its removable lumbar and leg supports, the driver can tailor the seat to their configuration and what suits their  driving style. The RTS is a wider version of the Mirco GT seat, and therefore more suitable for people of a larger physique. Thanks to the deep sitting position of the RTS, the driver can feel safe and comfortable in their seat and don't have to worry about moving around much. Monolithic construction seat: - Upholstered In velvet material- Made of high durability glass fiber reinforced plastic shell mould- 5 harness slots, can be used with 4, 5 or 6 point race harnesses- maximum recommended driver dimensions: ~ 100 kg / 190 cm Mirco RTS seat has the latest FIA homologation that allows you to take part in all FIA events across the World!!!





</Opis><Slike><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rts_69.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rts_77.jpg</value><value>https://mircoseats.com/galerie/m/mirco-rts_300.jpg</value></Slike><Features>Fixing: Side Weight: 8,8 kg Approval: FIA 8855-1999 Cover: Velour</Features></item>
</items>